[
  {
    "id": "000",
    "question": "What/Where/Why/When/How?",
    "answers": ["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "typeAnswer": [
      "Normal/Fire/Water/Grass/Electric/Ice/Fighting/Poison/Ground/Flying/Psychic/Bug/Rock/Ghost/Dragon/Dark/Steel/Fairy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "001",
    "question": "If you were out camping by the lake, which activity would you choose?",
    "answers": [
      "Swimming in the lake",
      "Taking a walk through the forest",
      "Camping by the campfire",
      "Sleeping"
    ],
    "typeAnswer": ["Water", "Grass", "Fire", "Normal"]
  },
  {
    "id": "002",
    "question": "Which of the following legendary pokemons would you choose?",
    "answers": ["Lugia", "Articuno", "Moltres", "Zapdos"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Psychic", "Ice", "Fire", "Electric"]
  },
  {
    "id": "003",
    "question": "If you had a choice of method to travel to your vacation destination, which one would you choose?",
    "answers": ["By plane", "By boat", "Walking/running", "By train"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Flying", "Water", "Normal", "Steel"]
  },
  {
    "id": "004",
    "question": "Which of the following festivals would you attend?",
    "answers": [
      "Christmas Festival",
      "Halloween Festival",
      "Bug Festival",
      "Dragon Festival"
    ],
    "typeAnswer": ["Ice", "Ghost", "Bug", "Dragon"]
  },
  {
    "id": "005",
    "question": "Which of the following anime do you prefer?",
    "answers": ["Fullmetal Alchemist", "Death Note", "One Piece", "Fairy Tail"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Poison", "Ghost", "Fighting", "Fairy"]
  },
  {
    "id": "006",
    "question": "Which of the following engineering disciplines best fits you?",
    "answers": [
      "Electrical Engineering",
      "Chemcial Engineering",
      "Enviromental Engineering",
      "Materials Engineering"
    ],
    "typeAnswer": ["Electric", "Poison", "Grass", "Rock"]
  },
  {
    "id": "007",
    "question": "What method of parcel delivery do you prefer?",
    "answers": ["Gound", "Air", "Ship", "Drone"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Ground", "Flying", "Water", "Electric"]
  },
  {
    "id": "008",
    "question": "In the anime, Avatar The Last Airbender, which bending style would best describe you?",
    "answers": ["Fire", "Water", "Air", "Earth"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Fire", "Water", "Flying", "Rock"]
  },
  {
    "id": "009",
    "question": "Which of the following color do you prefer?",
    "answers": ["Black", "Dark Blue", "Pink", "Red"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Dark", "Dragon", "Fairy", "Fighting"]
  },
  {
    "id": "010",
    "question": "Which type of dinosaur would you be?",
    "answers": ["Pterodactyl", "Mosasaurus", "Dilophosaurus", "Indominus Rex"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Flying", "Water", "Poison", "Fighting"]
  },
  {
    "id": "011",
    "question": "Which attack ability sounds best to you?",
    "answers": ["Snarl", "Aeroblast", "Shadow Claw", "Moonblast"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Dark", "Psychic", "Ghost", "Fairy"]
  },
  {
    "id": "012",
    "question": "Which attack ability sounds best to you?",
    "answers": [
      "Precipice Blades",
      "Flash Cannon",
      "Draco Meteor",
      "X-Scissor"
    ],
    "typeAnswer": ["Ground", "Steel", "Dragon", "Bug"]
  },
  {
    "id": "013",
    "question": "Which of the following activities do you prefer?",
    "answers": [
      "Ice Fishing",
      "Mountiain Climbing",
      "Motorcycle Stunt Through Fire",
      "Running"
    ],
    "typeAnswer": ["Ice", "Rock", "Fire", "Normal"]
  },
  {
    "id": "014",
    "question": "If you had a special power, which of the following would you choose?",
    "answers": [
      "Mind Reading",
      "Walk Through Walls",
      "Freeze Anything You Touch",
      "Poisonous Skin"
    ],
    "typeAnswer": ["Psychic", "Ghost", "Ice", "Poison"]
  },
  {
    "id": "015",
    "question": "Which of the following X-Men characters would you be?",
    "answers": ["Professor Xavier", "Magneto", "Nightcrawler", "Storm"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Psychic", "Steel", "Dark", "Electric"]
  },
  {
    "id": "016",
    "question": "Which of the following League of Legends champion do you prefer?",
    "answers": ["Blitzcrank", "Shyvana", "Zoe", "Kha'zix"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Steel", "Dragon", "Fairy", "Bug"]
  },
  {
    "id": "017",
    "question": "Which of the following Naruto character do you prefer?",
    "answers": ["Shino", "Itachi", "Gaara", "Fourth Raikage-A"],
    "typeAnswer": ["Bug", "Dark", "Ground", "Electric"]
  }
]
